

Kostiantyn Sakharov messengers: +380953979184

email: hellraisercw@gmail.com

LinkedIn

work examples: https://hellraisercw.github.io/

### **Profile**

Front-End Developer with a proven ability to collaborate effectively with senior developers while spending extra time to be mentored. Enjoy working closely with team members to ensure workloads are effectively redirected to bottlenecks and personally picking up the slack when necessary. With a passion for both personal growth and for software development, I attended a 100+ hours of lections and spent 500+ hours in coding bootcamps to learn new features while sharpening existing skills. Ready to apply my passion for coding to a talented engineering team to develop quality solutions for business purposes.

Area manager with over 11 years of experience in managing a division of over 170 people. Achieving set goals within the specified time frame.

Create, simplify ways of solving tasks to increase productivity and profitability. Excel in a rapidly changing environment and manage multiple projects from concept to implementation.

# **Professional Experience**

#### Student at EPAM Lab Ukraine

April 2022 - now

Area manager, Nova Poshta LLC, Kyiv, Ukraine

February 2019 - May 2022

Head of operations, Nova Poshta LLC, Kyiv, Ukraine

July 2016 - February 2019

Head of operations, Nova Poshta LLC, Dnipro, Ukraine

November 2011 - July 2016

Administration Manager, Cyber World, Dnipro, Ukraine

May 2005 - August 2011

### **Education**

#### **Bachelor of Business Administration and Management**

Prydniprovska State Academy of Civil Engineering and Architecture, Dnipro, Ukraine, 2002 – 2006.

## **Skills**

#### Technical:

HTML, CSS, JS, jQuery, Node.js, Angular.

#### Soft:

Communication, Teamwork, Responsibility, Growth mindset, Problem solving.